mimoco.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Mimoco

## Privacy Policy

Individual privacy is of great concern to Mimoco, as is your understanding of the ways we handle your personal information. We hope this brief statement will clearly describe how we make use of your information when you sign up for Mimoco news alerts or purchase goods on the Mimoco website.

The security of your information is important to us and your details are kept safe behind secure networks. We employ other companies to perform credit card processing on our behalf. These agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We promise not to sell or disclose your email or any personal information to any other third party without your consent. 

Mimoco does not buy, rent, or sell email addresses. Every email sent includes directions to unsubscribe, allowing users to immediately remove themselves from subscription. The only way to receive email news alerts is to subscribe. 

Mimoco complies with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

### To Unsubscribe

Users may always opt-out of receiving any mimoco emails by sending a message from the email address in question to [unsubscribe@mimoco.com](mailto:unsubscribe@mimoco.com).

If you have questions or are experiencing problems with unsubscribing, please send an email to [humanoid@mimoco.com](mailto:humanoid@mimoco.com).

We may from time to time revise this policy by updating this posting. Please check back for updates.

## Detecting and Preventing Fraud

In addition, this site collects, uses, and retains certain information about visitors to detect, prevent, and analyze fraudulent transactions. We share this information with a third party, Sift Science, Inc., that provides analysis, monitoring, and reports to assist us in preventing and detecting fraudulent transactions and other activity on the site.

The kinds of fraud-related information that we collect, retain, and share, in addition to how Sift Science uses and stores such information, are described by the Sift Science Service Privacy Notice. The Sift Science Service Privacy Notice is available online at <https://siftscience.com/service-privacy.html> and is incorporated here as a part of this privacy policy. You should review the Sift Science Service Privacy Notice carefully, understanding that “Client” refers to Mimoco, Inc and that Mimoco, Inc may collect and share all of the kinds of data described by the Sift Science Service Privacy Notice, including by means of Sift Science’s Application Programming Interface, JavaScript code, and other means. Statements in the Sift Science Privacy Notice about Sift Science, Inc.’s compliance with certain national or international privacy frameworks, including the European Union and Swiss “Safe Harbor” frameworks, apply to Sift Science, and not necessarily to Mimoco, Inc.

## Copyright

©2005-2015 Mimoco, Inc. All content on this site, including text, graphics, logos, icons, images, audio clips, and software, is the property of Mimoco, Inc. or its content licensors and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of Mimoco, Inc. and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. Mimoco, Inc, has a proprietary interest in its trademarks, service marks, trade names and trade dress including, but not limited to, Mimo™, MIMOBOT®, MimoPower®, MimoZine®, MimoByte®, MimoMicro®, ProtoHoodie®, the names Isadore, Ta2b, Galaxor, Magma, Vera, Jolibear, Protobot0, Protobot1, Fairybit Fairybot, Swirl, RayD8, Pupstar, Owsley Owlbert, Galacula, Psy, Ptry, The Clops Bros., Gigglebyte, Terry Le Bat, PowerSavers, AmpBurger, BotDog, CrayOn, DoobTube, DynOmite, FrankenToob, Larry LobstAh, Mummybot, Pawly PandAh, Pill Power, PowAh KowAh, PowerUp, Powly Owly, R0b0t0, Shocky Shark, SprayOn, Turbo Turtle, Zombie Finger, and the design of the characters and devices, which are protected by the U.S. and international laws. All other trademarks, service marks, trade names and trade dress are the property of their respective owners.
